that I have to do with him because he owns me.
he will make sure we will not   be with each other anymore.
If that's the last thing he does.
It was so extremely unpleasant and so eerie.
and just hear the voice of this crazy man.
just give me shivers, only I talk about it.
Here we start by notifying the clip.
But it obviously gets worse after that.
What do you think this person did?
He sits down for ten hours in a car to Stockholm.
Not just that.
He Bo sits in a hotel.
share on the corner.
Right near where we live.
We're starting to get planned when we got to watch this video.
actually did the crazy things he had also talked about.
Police told us.
to block him, ban him everywhere.
Give him no attention do not respond to any messages at all.
and whatever you do, don't talk about this out in your social media.
Because we don't know how to react if he would be angry.
and if he were to get angry what he would do then.
We got to sit there and just pretend, be happy that everything was peaceful and joyful.
It was great, very busy.
and at the same time it took a lot on our relationship between us.
for we walked around and was nerve wreck and worried.
and we couldn't sleep at night, and the smallest sound as we
heard or movement felt like he would break into our apartment.
and I think you noticed it more and more, to
Videos are getting smaller and smaller and my streams also.
It has been such a sick thing over our heads for so long.
I've been able to sit here now and do this.
I'm just so damn happy.
Yes, 100%
Now we really hope you want to accompany us on our journey back.
and you finally you at the truth.
to the big question that everyone has wondered.
are we still together?
Yes.
I didn't know what JI would do ...
Yes, we're still together.  *Laughter attack*